<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jubarly Studio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jubarly Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Abrasion Test</title>
      <link>/post/2021-02-27-abrasion-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021-02-27-abrasion-test/</guid>
      <description>Draft:
 I like illustrations and posters. About their punchiness. Oil painting needs conscious effort to be as punchy. How I tried to make it work: finelining and calligraphy. Are brush strokes and brush blends hidden?  Abrasion Test - oil on paper, 30 cm x 40 cm. Instagram link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye 2020 - New Year&#39;s cards for 2021</title>
      <link>/post/goodbye-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/goodbye-2020/</guid>
      <description>Almost every year, FC and I make Christmas or New Year&amp;rsquo;s cards for families and friends. At the end of 2020, when we tried to think through it retrospectively for design inspirations, the year seemed so dominated by Covid to the extent that not much else was there to talk about. Our only memorable part of 2020 was the summer months between the first wave and the second wave of the outbreak, when the situation was relatively calm, and we squeezed in two short trips to the Mediterranean Sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About this website</title>
      <link>/about-this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-this-website/</guid>
      <description>Goal This website introduces me, my artworks, and my artistic activities.
Introduction to myself See About me and Artist statement.
Post categories The blog posts are in 4 categories:
 General: about the website itself, me as a person and an artist, important updates etc. Artworks: introduction to a new work, work progress etc. Interviews: interviews of other artists or people in art business. Reviews: my reviews of exhibitions, shows, events etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website is ready</title>
      <link>/post/website-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/website-ready/</guid>
      <description>Today I finally figured out why I always got an error message when trying to configure the &amp;ldquo;custom resource records&amp;rdquo; in Google Domains&#39; DNS. I found this post and did the same mistake of overlooking a plus sign. I&amp;rsquo;ve just fixed it and now my website https://jubarlystudio.com/ is finally online.
I also added a top level post which is a short summary of this site: About this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep blue sea above the headboard</title>
      <link>/post/2021-01-24-deep-blue-sea-above-the-headboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021-01-24-deep-blue-sea-above-the-headboard/</guid>
      <description>Above the bed&amp;rsquo;s headboard in our bedroom, FC and I currently hang a small painting on the wall. It&amp;rsquo;s a 50 cm by 40 cm oil painting that I made in 2019. It looks like this:
An oil painting by myself (Spree at Night - oil on canvas, 50 cm x 40 cm, link to Instagram) is hanging on the wall above our headboard.
About a year ago, we started to have the idea of changing it to a larger painting, which would suit the size of wall better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Wei-Chun Chu is a visual artist working and living in Berlin.
Chu was born in Taipei, Taiwan. He developed a great interest in both art and science since childhood. At age of 18 he went to study physics at National Taiwan University. An year later he joined the university&amp;rsquo;s Fine Art Club and study oil painting under several tutors, including celebrity painter and songwriter Yu-Wei Hsieh and Chang-Lun Lin of the Rembrandt Art Studio in Taipei.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artist statement</title>
      <link>/artist-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist-statement/</guid>
      <description>As a visual artist, my greatest interest is to explore different light effects such as transmission, reflection, diffusion etc, in both representational and non-representational settings. In the representational setting, the primary theme of my works is the modern life of our time, particularly in Europe. With such a specific geographic scope, the aim is to capture the atmosphere and people&amp;rsquo;s daily activities, and very importantly, the rapid transformation of how we look and what we do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
