<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jubarly Studio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jubarly Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About this website</title>
      <link>/about-this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-this-website/</guid>
      <description>Goal This website introduces me, my artworks, and my artistic activities.
Introduction to myself See About me and Artist statement.
Post categories The blog posts are in 4 categories:
 General: about the website itself, me as a person and an artist, important updates etc. Artworks: introduction to a new work, work progress etc. Interviews: interviews of other artists or people in art business. Reviews: my reviews of exhibitions, shows, events etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website is ready</title>
      <link>/post/website-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/website-ready/</guid>
      <description>Today I finally figured out why I always got an error message when trying to configure the &amp;ldquo;custom resource records&amp;rdquo; in Google Domains&#39; DNS. I found this post and did the same mistake of overlooking a plus sign. I&amp;rsquo;ve just fixed it and now my website https://jubarlystudio.com/ is finally online.
I also added a top level post About this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep blue sea above the headboard</title>
      <link>/post/2021-01-24-deep-blue-sea-above-the-headboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021-01-24-deep-blue-sea-above-the-headboard/</guid>
      <description>Above the bed&amp;rsquo;s headboard in our bedroom, FC and I currently hang a small painting on the wall. It&amp;rsquo;s a 50 cm by 40 cm oil painting that I made in 2019. It looks like this:
An oil painting by myself (Spree at Night - oil on canvas, 50 cm x 40 cm, link to Instagram) is hanging on the wall above our headboard.
About a year ago, we started to have the idea of changing it to a larger painting, which would suit the size of wall better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Wei-Chun Chu is a visual artist working and living in Berlin.
Chu was born in Taipei, Taiwan. He developed a great interest in both art and science since childhood. At age of 18 he went to study physics at National Taiwan University. An year later he joined the university&amp;rsquo;s Fine Art Club and study oil painting under several tutors, including celebrity painter and songwriter Yu-Wei Hsieh and Chang-Lun Lin of the Rembrandt Art Studio in Taipei.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artist statement</title>
      <link>/artist-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artist-statement/</guid>
      <description>As a visual artist, my greatest interest is to explore different light effects such as transmission, reflection, diffusion etc, in both representational and non-representational settings. In the representational setting, the primary theme of my works is the modern life of our time, especially in Berlin. With such a specific geographic scope, the aim is to capture the atmosphere and people&amp;rsquo;s daily activities, and very importantly, the rapid transformation of the look of the city itself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
